Money Shot: The Pornhub Story is a documentary
film directed by Suzanne Hillinger.
Featuring interviews with performers, activists and past employees, this
documentary offers a deep dive into the successes and scandals of Pornhub.
Self - Porn Industry Professional, played by Noelle Perdue.
Self - Porn Industry Advocate / Director of Public
Affairs, FSC, played by Michael Stabile.
Self - Porn Performer, played by Siri Dahl.
Self - Porn Performer, played by Wolf Hudson.
Self - Journalist, The Logic, played by Martin Patriquin.
Self - Porn Director, played by Bree Mills.
Money Shot: The Pornhub Story is a 2023 Netflix documentary about
Pornhub and its parent company MindGeek (now Aylo).
It presents interview footage from sex workers, ex-Pornhub
employees, journalists, and anti-sex-trafficking figures.
The documentary focuses on a 2020 scandal over Pornhub hosting non-consensual pornography,
including of children, and how the aftermath affected pornographic performers.
When Netflix approached Jigsaw Productions about the film, director Suzanne Hillinger wanted to highlight sex
workers' opinions because she believed that they had been underrepresented in media coverage.
Hillinger said that many figures in the pornographic
industry were initially reluctant to participate.
Cherie DeVille was skeptical but participated to present the narrative
that anti-sex-trafficking groups had right-wing agendas.
Ex-Aylo employee Noelle Perdue worked as an archivist and
fact-checker, as well as being interviewed.
According to Rotten Tomatoes, most reviews of the documentary were positive.
However, reviewers were divided on many topics,
including the message, provenance, and pacing.
Some critics called it neutral, but others saw it as pro-sex work.
The focus on anti-sex-trafficking organizations' political aims was generally seen as a
strength, but some reviews criticized the interviews as lacking depth and a viewpoint.
Other reviewers concluded that Pornhub's content moderation was lacking and that there
are issues with the concentration of money and power in the industry.
The film explores themes of porn industry, porn
actress, adult filmmaking, onlyfans, porn.
The tone is thought_provoking.